webmeup.com 2017-06-06

# WebMeUp Privacy Policy

### WebMeUp Privacy Policy

#### What information do we collect?

The level of information WebMeUp collects depends on the level of your use. If you sign up to be a free, registered user of WebMeUp, you are required to enter your email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

If you sign up for a paid account, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. For your protection, WebMeUp does not store your billing information on its servers. WebMeUp partners with a secure payment gateway to provide a safe, secure payment procedure. 

WebMeUp offers a variety of online tools and software. These include, but are not limited to, our free SEO tools, our paid SEO tools, our API. These tools require you to enter a variety of information, such as URLs, domains, keywords, or other items relevant to Internet marketing and link research. We associate this information with your account in order to provide useful features, identify and terminate accounts that violate our Terms of Service, to improve our products, and to provide customer service. We never use this information for the provision of SEO consulting services so you do not need to worry that entering your information will be used against you or your clients by WebMeUp. 

####  What do we use your information for? 

WebMeUp uses collected information for the following general purposes: 

  * to personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * to improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 
  * to improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * to process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 
  * to send periodic emails 

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. You can unsubscribe from getting our e-mails at any moment. 

####  How do we protect your information? 

We use SSL encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information. 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

WebMeUp uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the WebMeUp application. The technical processing and transmission of the Service, including your content, may involve (a) transmissions over various networks, and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices. 

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure. 

####  Do we use cookies? 

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experience and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

####  Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

WebMeUp does not share your email address or other personally identifying information with any third parties, except our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, other valid legal processes, or when your actions violate the Terms of Service. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. 

####  Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

#### Third party advertising and analytics

We may allow third parties, including Google, to serve advertisements in connection with our Services and to provide analytics services. These third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information, such as your IP addresses, device identifiers, the browsers you use to visit our Services, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by WebMeUp and other companies to analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests and better understand your usage.

WebMeUp also uses third-party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the Internet. As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google's or any other third-party remarketing system. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service.

For Google's advertising network, you may adjust your advertising preferences by visiting the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/).

This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third party cookies, web beacons, or other tracking technologies, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of these third parties to learn more about their privacy practices.

####  California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel known as ‘My Account’ and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

####  Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy. 

####  Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

Last update 18/01/2013
